import ImageMagnifier from "../../common/ImageMagnifier";
import Separator from "../../common/Separator";
import { Card, Head, MapButton, Paragraph, Tip } from "../../common/TipsBuilder";
import Map from "../../../assets/img/jp/Japan_telephone_code_areas.svg";
import TrainingModal from "../../common/TrainingModal";

const aichi: Card[] = [
  { front: "052", back: "Aichi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0561", back: "Aichi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05613", back: "Aichi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05617", back: "Aichi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Ama District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0567", back: "Ama District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05675", back: "Ama District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05679", back: "Ama District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0566", back: "Anjo, Aichi" },
  { front: "05312", back: "Atsumi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05313", back: "Atsumi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "053145", back: "Atsumi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0566", back: "Chiryu, Aichi" },
  { front: "0562", back: "Chita District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0569", back: "Chita District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0562", back: "Chita, Aichi" },
  { front: "0569", back: "Chita, Aichi" },
  { front: "0533", back: "Gamagori, Aichi" },
  { front: "0586", back: "Haguri District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0569", back: "Handa, Aichi" },
  { front: "0566", back: "Hekinan, Aichi" },
  { front: "0564", back: "Higashikamo District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0565", back: "Higashikamo District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0533", back: "Hoi District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0586", back: "Ichinomiya, Aichi" },
  { front: "0586", back: "Inazawa, Aichi" },
  { front: "0587", back: "Inazawa, Aichi" },
  { front: "0568", back: "Inuyama, Aichi" },
  { front: "0587", back: "Iwakura, Aichi" },
  { front: "0566", back: "Kariya, Aichi" },
  { front: "0568", back: "Kasugai, Aichi" },
  { front: "05366", back: "Kitashitara District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05367", back: "Kitashitara District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05368", back: "Kitashitara District, Aichi" },
  { front: "053683", back: "Kitashitara District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0568", back: "Komaki, Aichi" },
  { front: "0587", back: "Konan, Aichi" },
  { front: "05363", back: "Minamishitara District, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Nagoya, Aichi" },
  { front: "0567", back: "Nakashima District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0587", back: "Nakashima District, Aichi" },
  { front: "05613", back: "Nishikamo District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0565", back: "Nishikamo District, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Nishikasugai District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0568", back: "Nishikasugai District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0563", back: "Nishio, Aichi hazu District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0586", back: "Nishio, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Nisshin, Aichi" },
  { front: "05617", back: "Nisshin, Aichi" },
  { front: "0587", back: "Niwa District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0564", back: "Nukata District, Aichi" },
  { front: "0562", back: "Obu, Aichi" },
  { front: "0564", back: "Okazaki, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Owariasahi, Aichi" },
  { front: "0561", back: "Owariasahi, Aichi" },
  { front: "0561", back: "Seto, Aichi" },
  { front: "0568", back: "Seto, Aichi" },
  { front: "05362", back: "Shinshiro, Aichi" },
  { front: "0566", back: "Takahama, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Tōkai, Aichi" },
  { front: "0562", back: "Tōkai, Aichi" },
  { front: "0569", back: "Tokoname, Aichi" },
  { front: "052", back: "Toyoake, Aichi" },
  { front: "0562", back: "Toyoake, Aichi" },
  { front: "0532", back: "Toyohashi, Aichi" },
  { front: "0533", back: "Toyokawa, Aichi" },
  { front: "0565", back: "Toyota, Aichi" },
  { front: "0567", back: "Tsushima, Aichi" },
];

const akita: Card[] = [
  { front: "0188", back: "Akita, Akita" },
  { front: "0182", back: "Hiraka District, Akita" },
  { front: "0184", back: "Honjo, Akita" },
  { front: "0188", back: "Kawabe District, Akita" },
  { front: "0176", back: "Kazuno District, Akita" },
  { front: "0186", back: "Kazuno, Akita" },
  { front: "0186", back: "Kitaakita District, Akita" },
  { front: "0185", back: "Minamiakita District, Akita" },
  { front: "0188", back: "Minamiakita District, Akita" },
  { front: "0185", back: "Noshiro, Akita" },
  { front: "0185", back: "Oga, Akita" },
  { front: "0182", back: "Ogachi District, Akita" },
  { front: "0183", back: "Ogachi District, Akita" },
  { front: "0186", back: "Ōdate, Akita" },
  { front: "0187", back: "Omagari, Akita" },
  { front: "0182", back: "Senboku District, Akita" },
  { front: "0187", back: "Senboku District, Akita" },
  { front: "0188", back: "Senboku District, Akita" },
  { front: "0185", back: "Yamamoto District, Akita" },
  { front: "0182", back: "Yokote, Akita" },
  { front: "0184", back: "Yuri District, Akita" },
  { front: "0183", back: "Yuzawa, Akita" },
];

const aomori: Card[] = [
  { front: "0172", back: "Aomori District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0177", back: "Aomori, Aomori" },
  { front: "0173", back: "Goshogawara, Aomori" },
  { front: "0178", back: "Hachinohe, Aomori" },
  { front: "0174", back: "Higashitsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0177", back: "Higashitsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0172", back: "Hirosaki, Aomori" },
  { front: "0176", back: "Kamikita District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0178", back: "Kamikita District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0172", back: "Kitatsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0173", back: "Kitatsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0172", back: "Kuroishi, Aomori" },
  { front: "0172", back: "Minamitsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0175", back: "Mutsu, Aomori" },
  { front: "0172", back: "Nakatsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0173", back: "Nishitsugaru District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0176", back: "Sannohe District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0178", back: "Sannohe District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0179", back: "Sannohe District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0175", back: "Shimokita District, Aomori" },
  { front: "0176", back: "Towada, Aomori" },
];

const chiba: Card[] = [
  { front: "0471", back: "Abiko, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Asahi, Chiba" },
  { front: "0470", back: "Awa District, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Chiba, Chiba" },
  { front: "0434", back: "Chiba, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Chiba, Chiba" },
  { front: "0475", back: "Chōsei District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Chōshi, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Funabashi, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Funabashi, Chiba" },
  { front: "0439", back: "Futtsu, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Higashikatsushika District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0471", back: "Higashikatsushika District, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Ichihara, Chiba" },
  { front: "0436", back: "Ichihara, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Ichikawa, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Inba District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Inba District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0476", back: "Inba District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0476", back: "Inzai, Chiba" },
  { front: "0470", back: "Isumi District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Kaijo District, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Kamagaya, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Kamagaya, Chiba" },
  { front: "0470", back: "Kamogawa, Chiba" },
  { front: "0471", back: "Kashiwa, Chiba" },
  { front: "0476", back: "Katori District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0478", back: "Katori District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Katori District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0470", back: "Katsuura, Chiba" },
  { front: "0439", back: "Kimitsu, Chiba" },
  { front: "0438", back: "Kisarazu, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Matsudo, Chiba" },
  { front: "0475", back: "Mobara, Chiba" },
  { front: "0471", back: "Nagareyama, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Narashino, Chiba" },
  { front: "0476", back: "Narita, Chiba" },
  { front: "0471", back: "Noda, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Sakura, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Sanbu District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0475", back: "Sanbu District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Sanbu District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0478", back: "Sawara, Chiba" },
  { front: "0438", back: "Sodegaura, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Sōsa District, Chiba" },
  { front: "0470", back: "Tateyama, Chiba" },
  { front: "047", back: "Urayasu, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Yachimata, Chiba" },
  { front: "0474", back: "Yachiyo, Chiba" },
  { front: "0479", back: "Yōkaichiba, Chiba" },
  { front: "043", back: "Yotsukaidō, Chiba" },
];

const ehime: Card[] = [
  { front: "0894", back: "Higashiuwa District, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Hōjō, Ehime" },
  { front: "0898", back: "Imabari, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Iyo District, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Iyo, Ehime" },
  { front: "0896", back: "Iyomishima, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Kamiukena District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0892", back: "Kamiukena District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0896", back: "Kawanoe, Ehime" },
  { front: "0893", back: "Kita District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0895", back: "Kitauwa District, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Matsuyama, Ehime" },
  { front: "0895", back: "Minamiuwa District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0897", back: "Niihama, Ehime" },
  { front: "0894", back: "Nishiuwa District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0897", back: "Ochi District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0898", back: "Ochi District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0893", back: "Ōzu, Ehime" },
  { front: "089", back: "Onsen District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0897", back: "Saijō, Ehime" },
  { front: "0897", back: "Shūsō District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0898", back: "Shūsō District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0898", back: "Tōyo, Ehime" },
  { front: "0896", back: "Uma District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0897", back: "Uma District, Ehime" },
  { front: "0895", back: "Uwajima, Ehime" },
  { front: "0894", back: "Yawatahama, Ehime" },
];

const fukui: Card[] = [
  { front: "07797", back: "Asuwa District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0776", back: "Fukui, Fukui" },
  { front: "0778", back: "Imadate District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0779", back: "Katsuyama, Fukui" },
  { front: "0770", back: "Mikata District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0778", back: "Nanjō District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0776", back: "Nyū District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0778", back: "Nyū District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0770", back: "Obama, Fukui" },
  { front: "0770", back: "Ōi District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0779", back: "Ōno District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0779", back: "Ono, Fukui" },
  { front: "0770", back: "Onyu District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0778", back: "Sabae, Fukui" },
  { front: "0776", back: "Sakai District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0778", back: "Takefu, Fukui" },
  { front: "0770", back: "Tsuruga, Fukui" },
  { front: "0776", back: "Yoshida District, Fukui" },
  { front: "0779", back: "Yoshida District, Fukui" },
];

const fukuoka: Card[] = [
  { front: "0946", back: "Amagi, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Asakura District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09437", back: "Asakura District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0946", back: "Asakura District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0979", back: "Buzen, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Chikugo, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Chikugo, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09305", back: "Chikujō District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0979", back: "Chikujō District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Chikushi District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Chikushino, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Dazaifu, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Fukuoka, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0940", back: "Fukutsu, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0948", back: "Iizuka, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09496", back: "Iizuka, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Itoshima District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0948", back: "Kaho District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09496", back: "Kaho District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Kasuga, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Kasuya District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093", back: "Kitakyushu, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Koga, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09492", back: "Kurate District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09493", back: "Kurate District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Kurume, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Maebaru, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Mii District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Miike District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093", back: "Miyako District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09302", back: "Miyako District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093032", back: "Miyako District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093033", back: "Miyako District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09304", back: "Miyako District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Miyama, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Miyama, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Mizuma District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Mizuma District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0940", back: "Munakata, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093", back: "Nakama, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0947", back: "Nogata, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09492", back: "Nogata, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Ogori, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Ogori, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Okawa, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Omuta, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "092", back: "Onojo, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "093", back: "Onga District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0947", back: "Tagawa District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0947", back: "Tagawa, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "09437", back: "Ukiha District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0946", back: "Ukiha District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0948", back: "Yamada, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Yame District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0943", back: "Yame District, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0943", back: "Yame, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Yanagawa, Fukuoka" },
  { front: "0930", back: "Yukuhashi, Fukuoka" },
];

const fukushima: Card[] = [
  { front: "024", back: "Adachi District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0243", back: "Adachi District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Aizuwakamatsu, Fukushima" },
  { front: "024", back: "Date District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "024", back: "Fukushima, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Fukushima, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0243", back: "Fukushima, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0240", back: "Futaba District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0244", back: "Haramachi, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0247", back: "Higashishirakawa District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0247", back: "Ishikawa District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0246", back: "Iwaki, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0248", back: "Iwase District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0241", back: "Kawanuma District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Kawanuma District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Kitaaizu District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0241", back: "Kitakata, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0249", back: "Kōriyama, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0241", back: "Minamiaizu District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0243", back: "Nihonmatsu, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0248", back: "Nishishirakawa District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0241", back: "Ōnuma District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Ōnuma District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0248", back: "Shirakawa, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0244", back: "Sōma District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0244", back: "Souma, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0248", back: "Sukagawa, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0249", back: "Sukagawa, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0247", back: "Tamura District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0249", back: "Tamura District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0241", back: "Yama District, Fukushima" },
  { front: "0242", back: "Yama District, Fukushima" },
];

const gifu: Card[] = [
  { front: "0584", back: "Anpachi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0585", back: "Anpachi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0572", back: "Ena District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0573", back: "Ena District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0573", back: "Ena, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Fuwa District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058", back: "Gifu, Gifu" },
  { front: "0575", back: "Gujo District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058", back: "Hashima District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058689", back: "Hashima District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058", back: "Hashima, Gifu" },
  { front: "058139", back: "Ibi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Ibi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0585", back: "Ibi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Kaizu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0583", back: "Kakamigahara, Gifu" },
  { front: "0574", back: "Kamo District, Gifu" },
  { front: "05747", back: "Kamo District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0574", back: "Kani District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0574", back: "Kani, Gifu" },
  { front: "0576", back: "Mashita District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0575", back: "Mino, Gifu" },
  { front: "0574", back: "Minokamo, Gifu" },
  { front: "0572", back: "Mizunami, Gifu" },
  { front: "0573", back: "Mizunami, Gifu" },
  { front: "0574", back: "Mizunami, Gifu" },
  { front: "058", back: "Motosu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0581", back: "Motosu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058138", back: "Motosu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Motosu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0585", back: "Motosu District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0575", back: "Mugi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058157", back: "Mugi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "058158", back: "Mugi District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0573", back: "Nakatsugawa, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Ogaki, Gifu" },
  { front: "0576", back: "Ōno District, Gifu" },
  { front: "05769", back: "Ōno District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0577", back: "Ōno District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0763", back: "Ōno District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0575", back: "Seki, Gifu" },
  { front: "0572", back: "Tajimi, Gifu" },
  { front: "0577", back: "Takayama, Gifu" },
  { front: "0572", back: "Toki District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0572", back: "Toki, Gifu" },
  { front: "0581", back: "Yamagata District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0584", back: "Yoro District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0577", back: "Yoshiki District, Gifu" },
  { front: "0578", back: "Yoshiki District, Gifu" },
];

const gunma: Card[] = [
  { front: "0267", back: "Agatsuma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0279", back: "Agatsuma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Agatsuma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Annaka, Gunma" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Fujioka, Gunma" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Gunma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0270", back: "Isesaki, Gunma" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Kanra District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Kanra District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0277", back: "Kiryū, Gunma" },
  { front: "027", back: "Kitagunma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0279", back: "Kitagunma District, Gunma" },
  { front: "027", back: "Maebashi, Gunma" },
  { front: "0276", back: "Nitta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0277", back: "Nitta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Nitta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0278", back: "Numata, Gunma" },
  { front: "0276", back: "Ohta, Gunma" },
  { front: "0284", back: "Ohta, Gunma" },
  { front: "0276", back: "Ōra District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0270", back: "Sawa District, Gunma" },
  { front: "027", back: "Seta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0277", back: "Seta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0279", back: "Seta District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0279", back: "Shibukawa, Gunma" },
  { front: "027", back: "Takasaki, Gunma" },
  { front: "027", back: "Tano District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Tano District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0276", back: "Tatebayashi, Gunma" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Tomioka, Gunma" },
  { front: "0278", back: "Tone District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Usui District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0273", back: "Usui District, Gunma" },
  { front: "0277", back: "Yamada District, Gunma" },
];

const hiroshima: Card[] = [
  { front: "082", back: "Aki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0823", back: "Aki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0847", back: "Ashina District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0847", back: "Fuchuu, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0849", back: "Fukayasu District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0847", back: "Fukuyama, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0849", back: "Fukuyama, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Futami District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082", back: "Hatsukaichi, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08248", back: "Hiba District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082485", back: "Hiba District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082486", back: "Hiba District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08477", back: "Hiba District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Higashihiroshima, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082", back: "Hiroshima, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08452", back: "Innoshima, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08478", back: "Jinseki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0823", back: "Kamo District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Kamo District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08473", back: "Kamo District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082488", back: "Kōnu District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "084762", back: "Kōnu District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "084767", back: "Kōnu District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0823", back: "Kure, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0848", back: "Mihara, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "084732", back: "Mitsugi District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0848", back: "Mitsugi District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08487", back: "Mitsugi District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Miyoshi, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0826", back: "Miyoshi, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0849", back: "Numakuma District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08275", back: "Ōtake, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0848", back: "Onomichi, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0823", back: "Saeki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08262", back: "Saeki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08275", back: "Saeki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0829", back: "Saeki District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08472", back: "Sera District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08473", back: "Sera District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08247", back: "Shōbara, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "082488", back: "Shōbara, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Takata District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0826", back: "Takata District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0846", back: "Takehara, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0823", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0824", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08452", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0846", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08466", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "084732", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0848", back: "Toyota District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "0826", back: "Yamagata District, Hiroshima" },
  { front: "08262", back: "Yamagata District, Hiroshima" },
];

const hokkaido: Card[] = [
  { front: "0152", back: "Abashiri District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01527", back: "Abashiri District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0136", back: "Abuta District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0142", back: "Abuta District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Akabira, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0154", back: "Akan District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0153", back: "Akkeshi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0166", back: "Asahikawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01242", back: "Ashibetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0167", back: "Ashibetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01562", back: "Ashoro District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0133", back: "Atsuta District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01337", back: "Atsuta District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01266", back: "Bibai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0123", back: "Chitose, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01452", back: "Chitose, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0142", back: "Date, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "011", back: "Ebetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0123", back: "Eniwa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01634", back: "Esashi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01636", back: "Esashi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0164", back: "Fukagawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0167", back: "Furano, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0135", back: "Furuu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0138", back: "Hakodate, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "013379", back: "Hamamasu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01558", back: "Hiroo District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01395", back: "Hiyama District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01396", back: "Hiyama District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01466", back: "Horoizumi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0126", back: "Ishikari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0133", back: "Ishikari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01332", back: "Ishikari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0133", back: "Ishikari, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0136", back: "Isoya District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0126", back: "Iwamizawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01267", back: "Iwamizawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0135", back: "Iwanai District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Kabato District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0126", back: "Kabato District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0138", back: "Kameda District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0138", back: "Kamiiso District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01392", back: "Kamiiso District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01548", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01566", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "016528", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "016532", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "016534", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01655", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01658", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0166", back: "Kamikawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0155", back: "Kasai District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01564", back: "Katō District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01566", back: "Katō District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01237", back: "Kayabe District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01372", back: "Kayabe District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01374", back: "Kayabe District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "011", back: "Kitahiroshima, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0157", back: "Kitami, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01398", back: "Kudō District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0154", back: "Kushiro District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0154", back: "Kushiro, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0164", back: "Mashike District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01394", back: "Matsumae District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01538", back: "Menashi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01267", back: "Mikasa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01463", back: "Mitsuishi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "015829", back: "Monbetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01584", back: "Monbetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01586", back: "Monbetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01587", back: "Monbetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01588", back: "Monbetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01582", back: "Monbetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0143", back: "Muroran, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0155", back: "Nakagawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01557", back: "Nakagawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01562", back: "Nakagawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01656", back: "Nakagawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01654", back: "Nayoro, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01532", back: "Nemuro, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01456", back: "Niikappu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01464", back: "Niikappu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01396", back: "Nishi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01398", back: "Nishi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0143", back: "Noboribetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01537", back: "Notsuke District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01538", back: "Notsuke District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0155", back: "Obihiro, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01397", back: "Okushiri District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0133", back: "Otaru, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0134", back: "Otaru, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01638", back: "Rebun District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01638", back: "Rishiri District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01645", back: "Rumoi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0164", back: "Rumoi, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01463", back: "Samani District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "011", back: "Sapporo, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01456", back: "Saru District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01457", back: "Saru District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01378", back: "Setana District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0135", back: "Shakotan District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0152", back: "Shari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01522", back: "Shari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01538", back: "Shibetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01652", back: "Shibetsu, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01537", back: "Shibetsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0136", back: "Shimamaki District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01547", back: "Shiranuka District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0144", back: "Shiraoi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01464", back: "Shizunai District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "011", back: "Sorachi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Sorachi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0126", back: "Sorachi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0167", back: "Sorachi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01635", back: "Sōya District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Sunagawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0136", back: "Suttsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Takikawa, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0162", back: "Teshio District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01632", back: "Teshio District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01557", back: "Tokachi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0152", back: "Tokoro District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0157", back: "Tokoro District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0123", back: "Tomakomai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0144", back: "Tomakomai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01452", back: "Tomakomai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01646", back: "Tomamae District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01648", back: "Tomamae District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01462", back: "Urakawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01463", back: "Urakawa District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Uryū District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0164", back: "Uryū District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01653", back: "Uryū District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0136", back: "Usu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0142", back: "Usu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0125", back: "Utashinai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0162", back: "Wakkanai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01635", back: "Wakkanai, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01376", back: "Yamakoshi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01377", back: "Yamakoshi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0135", back: "Yoichi District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01237", back: "Yūbari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01238", back: "Yūbari District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01235", back: "Yūbari, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01237", back: "Yūbari, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01452", back: "Yūfutsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "01454", back: "Yūfutsu District, Hokkaidō" },
  { front: "0167", back: "Yūfutsu District, Hokkaidō" },
];

const hyogo: Card[] = [
  { front: "07912", back: "Aioi, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "078", back: "Akashi, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "07915", back: "Akō District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "07914", back: "Ako, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "06", back: "Amagasaki, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Asago District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0797", back: "Ashiya, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0798", back: "Ashiya, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Hikami District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0792", back: "Himeji, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0791", back: "Ibo District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0792", back: "Ibo District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "07932", back: "Ibo District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "06", back: "Itami, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Itami, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Izushi District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "078", back: "Kako District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Kako District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Kako District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "078", back: "Kakogawa, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Kakogawa, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0790", back: "Kanzaki District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0792", back: "Kanzaki District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0790", back: "Kasai, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Kawabe District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Kawanishi, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Kinosaki District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "078", back: "Kobe, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0797", back: "Kobe, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0799", back: "Mihara District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Mikata District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Miki, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Mino District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "078", back: "Nishinomiya, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0797", back: "Nishinomiya, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0798", back: "Nishinomiya, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Nishiwaki, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Ono, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Ono, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Sanda, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0790", back: "Sayō District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "07932", back: "Shikama District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "07933", back: "Shikama District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0790", back: "Shisō District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0799", back: "Sumoto, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0795", back: "Taka District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0797", back: "Takarazuka, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0798", back: "Takarazuka, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Takarazuka, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0794", back: "Takasago, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0791", back: "Tatsuno, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Toyooka, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0799", back: "Tsuna District, Hyōgo" },
  { front: "0796", back: "Yabu District, Hyōgo" },
];

const ibaraki: Card[] = [
  { front: "029", back: "Higashiibaraki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "02955", back: "Higashiibaraki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0294", back: "Hitachi, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "029", back: "Hitachinaka, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0294", back: "Hitachiōta, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Inashiki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0298", back: "Inashiki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Inashiki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Ishioka, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Iwai, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Kasama, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0291", back: "Kashima District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Kashima District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0478", back: "Kashima District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Kashima, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0293", back: "Kitaibaraki, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Kitasouma District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0280", back: "Koga, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0294", back: "Kuji District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "02957", back: "Kuji District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Makabe District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "029", back: "Mito, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Mitsukaido, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "029", back: "Naka District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0292", back: "Naka District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0294", back: "Naka District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "02955", back: "Naka District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0291", back: "Namegata District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Namegata District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0478", back: "Namegata District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0298", back: "Niihari District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Niihari District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Nishiibaraki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0299", back: "Nishiibaraki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Ryūgasaki, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0280", back: "Sashima District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Shimodate, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Shimotsuma, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0293", back: "Taga District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0293", back: "Takahagi, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Toride, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0471", back: "Toride, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0298", back: "Tsuchiura, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Tsukuba District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0298", back: "Tsukuba, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0298", back: "Ushiku, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Yūki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0297", back: "Yūki District, Ibaraki" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Yuki, Ibaraki" },
];

const ishikawa: Card[] = [
  { front: "07617", back: "Enuma District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0768", back: "Fugeshi District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Hakui, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0767", back: "Hakui, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "076", back: "Ishikawa District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "07619", back: "Ishikawa District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "07617", back: "Kaga, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "076", back: "Kahoku District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0767", back: "Kanazawa, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0767", back: "Kashima District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0761", back: "Komatsu, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "076", back: "Matto, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0767", back: "Nanao, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "076", back: "Nomi District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0761", back: "Nomi District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "07619", back: "Nomi District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0768", back: "Suzu District, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0768", back: "Suzu, Ishikawa" },
  { front: "0768", back: "Wajima, Ishikawa" },
];

const iwate: Card[] = [
  { front: "0197", back: "Esashi, Iwate" },
  { front: "0198", back: "Hanamaki, Iwate" },
  { front: "0198", back: "Hienuki District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0191", back: "Ichinoseki, Iwate" },
  { front: "0197", back: "Isawa District, Iwate" },
  { front: "019", back: "Iwate District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0195", back: "Iwate District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0193", back: "Kamaishi, Iwate" },
  { front: "0193", back: "Kamihei District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0194", back: "Kamihei District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0198", back: "Kamihei District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0191", back: "Kesen District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0192", back: "Kesen District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0197", back: "Kesen District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0197", back: "Kitakami, Iwate" },
  { front: "0194", back: "Kuji, Iwate" },
  { front: "0194", back: "Kunohe District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0195", back: "Kunohe District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0193", back: "Miyako, Iwate" },
  { front: "0197", back: "Mizusawa, Iwate" },
  { front: "019", back: "Morioka, Iwate" },
  { front: "0195", back: "Ninohe District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0195", back: "Ninohe, Iwate" },
  { front: "0191", back: "Nishiiwai District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0192", back: "Ōfunato, Iwate" },
  { front: "0192", back: "Rikuzentakata, Iwate" },
  { front: "019", back: "Shiwa District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0198", back: "Tōno, Iwate" },
  { front: "0198", back: "Waga District, Iwate" },
  { front: "0197", back: "Waga District, Iwate" },
];

const kagawa: Card[] = [
  { front: "087", back: "Ayauta District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0877", back: "Ayauta District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "087", back: "Kagawa District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0875", back: "Kanonji, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0877", back: "Marugame, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0875", back: "Mitoyo District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0896", back: "Mitoyo District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0877", back: "Nakatado District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "087", back: "Okawa District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0879", back: "Okawa District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0877", back: "Sakaide, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0879", back: "Shozu District, Kagawa" },
  { front: "087", back: "Takamatsu, Kagawa" },
  { front: "0877", back: "Zentsuji, Kagawa" },
];

const kagoshima: Card[] = [
  { front: "099", back: "Aira District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0995", back: "Aira District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Akune, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "099", back: "Hioki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Hioki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Hioki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Ibusuki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Ibusuki, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09952", back: "Isa District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Izumi District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Izumi, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "099", back: "Kagoshima District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09912", back: "Kagoshima District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09913", back: "Kagoshima District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "099", back: "Kagoshima, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0994", back: "Kanoya, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Kaseda, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0933", back: "Kawanabe District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Kawanabe District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0994", back: "Kimotsuki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09942", back: "Kimotsuki District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0995", back: "Kokubu, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09972", back: "Kumage District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09974", back: "Kumage District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Kushikino, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0993", back: "Makurazaki, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0997", back: "Naze, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09952", back: "Okuchi, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0997", back: "Ōshima District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09977", back: "Ōshima District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Satsuma District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "09969", back: "Satsuma District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0996", back: "Sendai, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0986", back: "Soo District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0994", back: "Soo District, Kagoshima" },
  { front: "0994", back: "Tarumizu, Kagoshima" },
];

const kanagawa: Card[] = [
  { front: "0462", back: "Aikō District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0460", back: "Ashigarashimo District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0465", back: "Ashigarashimo District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0462", back: "Atsugi, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0467", back: "Ayase, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0467", back: "Chigasaki, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0462", back: "Ebina, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0466", back: "Fujisawa, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0463", back: "Hadano, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0463", back: "Hiratsuka, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0463", back: "Isehara, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0467", back: "Kamakura, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Kawasaki, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "044", back: "Kawasaki, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0467", back: "Koza District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0465", back: "Minamiashigara, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0468", back: "Miura District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0468", back: "Miura, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0463", back: "Naka District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0465", back: "Naka District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0465", back: "Odawara, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Sagamihara, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0462", back: "Sagamihara, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0426", back: "Tsukui District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Tsukui District, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0462", back: "Yamato, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Yokohama, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "044", back: "Yokohama, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "045", back: "Yokohama, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0468", back: "Yokosuka, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Zama, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0462", back: "Zama, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0467", back: "Zushi, Kanagawa" },
  { front: "0468", back: "Zushi, Kanagawa" },
];

const kochi: Card[] = [
  { front: "0888", back: "Agawa District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0889", back: "Agawa District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08872", back: "Aki District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08873", back: "Aki District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08874", back: "Aki District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08873", back: "Aki, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0880", back: "Hata District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08802", back: "Hata District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08875", back: "Kami District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Kami District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Kōchi, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08872", back: "Muroto, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0887", back: "Nagaoka District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08875", back: "Nagaoka District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0880", back: "Nakamura, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Nankoku, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0880", back: "Sukumo, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Susaki, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0889", back: "Susaki, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08802", back: "Takaoka District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0889", back: "Takaoka District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0887", back: "Tosa District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Tosa District, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0888", back: "Tosa, Kōchi" },
  { front: "08808", back: "Tosashimizu, Kōchi" },
  { front: "0880", back: "Tosashimizu, Kōchi" },
];

const kumamoto: Card[] = [
  { front: "0964", back: "Amakusa District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0969", back: "Amakusa District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "09697", back: "Amakusa District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0944", back: "Arao, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0966", back: "Ashikita District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Aso District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0967", back: "Aso District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "09676", back: "Aso District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0973", back: "Aso District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0966", back: "Hitoyoshi, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0969", back: "Hondo, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Kamimashiki District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0967", back: "Kamimashiki District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Kamoto District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Kamoto District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Kikuchi District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Kikuchi District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Kikuchi, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0966", back: "Kuma District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Kumamoto, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0966", back: "Minamata, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "096", back: "Shimomashiki District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0964", back: "Shimomashiki District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Tamana District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Tamana, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "09697", back: "Ushibuka, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0964", back: "Uto District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0964", back: "Uto, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0968", back: "Yamaga, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0964", back: "Yatsushiro District, Kumamoto" },
  { front: "0965", back: "Yatsushiro, Kumamoto" },
];

const kyoto: Card[] = [
  { front: "0773", back: "Amata District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0773", back: "Ayabe, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0773", back: "Fukuchiyama, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0771", back: "Funai District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Jōyō, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0771", back: "Kameoka, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0773", back: "Kasa District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0771", back: "Kitakuwada District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0772", back: "Kumano District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Kuse District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Kuse District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Kyōtanabe, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0726", back: "Kyoto, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Kyoto, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0775", back: "Kyoto, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0773", back: "Maizuru, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0772", back: "Miyazu, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Mukō, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Nagaokakyō, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0772", back: "Naka District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Otokuni District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "07439", back: "Soraku District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "074395", back: "Soraku District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Soraku District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0772", back: "Takeno District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Tsuzuki District, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0774", back: "Uji, Kyoto" },
  { front: "075", back: "Yawata, Kyoto" },
  { front: "0772", back: "Yosa District, Kyoto" },
];

const mie: Card[] = [
  { front: "059", back: "Age District, Mie" },
  { front: "0595", back: "Ayama District, Mie" },
  { front: "059", back: "Hisai, Mie" },
  { front: "059", back: "Ichishi District, Mie" },
  { front: "0598", back: "Ichishi District, Mie" },
  { front: "05984", back: "Ichishi District, Mie" },
  { front: "059856", back: "Ichishi District, Mie" },
  { front: "059832", back: "Iinan District, Mie" },
  { front: "05984", back: "Iinan District, Mie" },
  { front: "0594", back: "Inabe District, Mie" },
  { front: "0596", back: "Ise, Mie" },
  { front: "0599", back: "Ise, Mie" },
  { front: "05958", back: "Kameyama, Mie" },
  { front: "05973", back: "Kitamuro District, Mie" },
  { front: "05974", back: "Kitamuro District, Mie" },
  { front: "05978", back: "Kumano, Mie" },
  { front: "0567", back: "Kuwana District, Mie" },
  { front: "0594", back: "Kuwana District, Mie" },
  { front: "0594", back: "Kuwana, Mie" },
  { front: "0598", back: "Matsusaka, Mie" },
  { front: "0593", back: "Mie District, Mie" },
  { front: "05979", back: "Minamimuro District, Mie" },
  { front: "0735", back: "Minamimuro District, Mie" },
  { front: "07354", back: "Minamimuro District, Mie" },
  { front: "0595", back: "Nabari, Mie" },
  { front: "0595", back: "Naga District, Mie" },
  { front: "05972", back: "Owase, Mie" },
  { front: "05994", back: "Shima District, Mie" },
  { front: "05995", back: "Shima District, Mie" },
  { front: "05997", back: "Shima District, Mie" },
  { front: "05998", back: "Shima District, Mie" },
  { front: "05959", back: "Suzuka District, Mie" },
  { front: "0593", back: "Suzuka, Mie" },
  { front: "0596", back: "Taki District, Mie" },
  { front: "05983", back: "Taki District, Mie" },
  { front: "059849", back: "Taki District, Mie" },
  { front: "05987", back: "Taki District, Mie" },
  { front: "05988", back: "Taki District, Mie" },
  { front: "0599", back: "Toba, Mie" },
  { front: "05995", back: "Toba, Mie" },
  { front: "059", back: "Tsu, Mie" },
  { front: "0595", back: "Ueno, Mie" },
  { front: "05987", back: "Watarai District, Mie" },
  { front: "059872", back: "Watarai District, Mie" },
  { front: "05988", back: "Watarai District, Mie" },
  { front: "05996", back: "Watarai District, Mie" },
  { front: "0593", back: "Yokkaichi, Mie" },
];

const miyagi: Card[] = [
  { front: "0229", back: "Furukawa, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0224", back: "Igu District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0244", back: "Igu District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Ishinomaki, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0223", back: "Iwanuma, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0224", back: "Kakuda, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0229", back: "Kami District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0224", back: "Katta District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0226", back: "Kesennuma, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0228", back: "Kurihara District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "022", back: "Kurokawa District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Miyagi District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Monou District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Motoyoshi District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0226", back: "Motoyoshi District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "022", back: "Natori, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0223", back: "Natori, Miyagi" },
  { front: "023", back: "Natori, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Oshika District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "022", back: "Sendai, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0224", back: "Shibata District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0229", back: "Shida District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "022", back: "Shiogama, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0224", back: "Shiroishi, Miyagi" },
  { front: "022", back: "Tagajō, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0229", back: "Tamatsukuri District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Tōda District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0229", back: "Tōda District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0220", back: "Tome District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0225", back: "Tome District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0228", back: "Tome District, Miyagi" },
  { front: "0223", back: "Watari District, Miyagi" },
];

const miyazaki: Card[] = [
  { front: "0984", back: "Ebino, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0984", back: "Higashimorokata District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0985", back: "Higashimorokata District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Higashiusuki District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0983", back: "Higashiusuki District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Hyuuga, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0986", back: "Kitamorokata District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0984", back: "Kobayashi, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0966", back: "Koyu District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Koyu District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0983", back: "Koyu District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0985", back: "Koyu District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0987", back: "Kushima, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0987", back: "Minaminaka District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0986", back: "Miyakonojo, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0985", back: "Miyazaki District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0985", back: "Miyazaki, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0987", back: "Nichinan, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0984", back: "Nishimorokata District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Nishiusuki District, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Nobeoka, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0983", back: "Saito, Miyazaki" },
  { front: "0985", back: "Saito, Miyazaki" },
];

const nagano: Card[] = [
  { front: "0267", back: "Chiisagata District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Chiisagata District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Chino, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Hanishina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Hanishina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0263", back: "Higashichikuma District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0265", back: "Iida, Nagano" },
  { front: "0269", back: "Iiyama, Nagano" },
  { front: "0265", back: "Ina, Nagano" },
  { front: "0265", back: "Kamiina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Kamiina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Kamiminochi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Kamitakai District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0264", back: "Kiso District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0573", back: "Kiso District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Kitaazumi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0261", back: "Kitaazumi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Kitasaku District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Kitasaku District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0265", back: "Komagane, Nagano" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Komoro, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Koshoku, Nagano" },
  { front: "0263", back: "Matsumoto, Nagano" },
  { front: "0263", back: "Minamiazumi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Minamisaku District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Minamisaku District, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Nagano, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Nagano, Nagano" },
  { front: "0269", back: "Nakano, Nagano" },
  { front: "0261", back: "Ōmachi, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Okaya, Nagano" },
  { front: "0267", back: "Saku, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Sarashina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Sarashina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0260", back: "Shimoina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0265", back: "Shimoina District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Shimominochi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0269", back: "Shimominochi District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0269", back: "Shimotakai District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0263", back: "Shiojiri, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Shiojiri, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Suwa District, Nagano" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Suwa, Nagano" },
  { front: "026", back: "Suzaka, Nagano" },
  { front: "0268", back: "Ueda, Nagano" },
];

const nagasaki: Card[] = [
  { front: "0959", back: "Fukue, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0956", back: "Higashisonogi District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Higashisonogi District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0950", back: "Hirado, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "09204", back: "Iki, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Isahaya, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "09208", back: "Kamiagata District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0950", back: "Kitamatsuura District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0956", back: "Kitamatsuura District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0959", back: "Kitamatsuura District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Kitatakaki District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0956", back: "Matsuura, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0959", back: "Minamimatsura District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Minamitakaki District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "095", back: "Nagasaki, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "095", back: "Nishisonogi District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Nishisonogi District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0959", back: "Nishisonogi District, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Omura, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0956", back: "Sasebo, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "0957", back: "Shimabara, Nagasaki" },
  { front: "09205", back: "Shimoagata District, Nagasaki" },
];

const nara: Card[] = [
  { front: "07472", back: "Gojō, Nara" },
  { front: "0721", back: "Gose, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Gose, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Ikoma District, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Ikoma District, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Ikoma, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Kashiba, Nara" },
  { front: "0744", back: "Kashihara, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Kitakatsuragi District, Nara" },
  { front: "0742", back: "Nara, Nara" },
  { front: "0744", back: "Sakurai, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Shiki District, Nara" },
  { front: "07443", back: "Shiki District, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Shiki District, Nara" },
  { front: "07439", back: "Soekami District, Nara" },
  { front: "0744", back: "Takaichi District, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Takaichi District, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Tenri, Nara" },
  { front: "059", back: "Uda District, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Uda District, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Uda District, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Yamabe District, Nara" },
  { front: "0743", back: "Yamatokōriyama, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Yamatotakada, Nara" },
  { front: "07354", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
  { front: "0744", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
  { front: "0745", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
  { front: "07463", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
  { front: "0747", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
  { front: "07473", back: "Yoshino District, Nara" },
];

const niigata: Card[] = [
  { front: "0255", back: "Arai, Niigata" },
  { front: "0250", back: "Gosen, Niigata" },
  { front: "02549", back: "Higashikanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Higashikubiki District, Niigata" },
  { front: "02559", back: "Higashikubiki District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Itoigawa, Niigata" },
  { front: "0235", back: "Iwafune District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0254", back: "Iwafune District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Jōetsu, Niigata" },
  { front: "0256", back: "Kamo, Niigata" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Kariwa District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Kariwa District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Kashiwazaki, Niigata" },
  { front: "025", back: "Kitakanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0254", back: "Kitakanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "02579", back: "Kitauonuma District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Kitauonuma District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Koshi District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0256", back: "Minamikanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Minamiuonuma District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Minamiuonuma District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Mitsuke, Niigata" },
  { front: "0254", back: "Murakami, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Nagaoka, Niigata" },
  { front: "0250", back: "Nakakanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Nakakubiki District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Nakauonuma District, Niigata" },
  { front: "025", back: "Niigata, Niigata" },
  { front: "0250", back: "Niitsu, Niigata" },
  { front: "025", back: "Nishikanbara District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0255", back: "Nishikubiki District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Ojiya, Niigata" },
  { front: "0259", back: "Ryotsu, Niigata" },
  { front: "0259", back: "Sado, Niigata" },
  { front: "0256", back: "Sanjō, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Santō District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0256", back: "Sato District, Niigata" },
  { front: "0254", back: "Shibata, Niigata" },
  { front: "025", back: "Shirone, Niigata" },
  { front: "0258", back: "Tochio, Niigata" },
  { front: "0257", back: "Tōkamachi, Niigata" },
  { front: "025", back: "Toyosaka, Niigata" },
  { front: "0256", back: "Tsubame, Niigata" },
];

const oita: Card[] = [
  { front: "0977", back: "Beppu, Ōita" },
  { front: "0978", back: "Bungotakada, Ōita" },
  { front: "0977", back: "Hayami District, Ōita" },
  { front: "09786", back: "Higashikunisaki District, Ōita" },
  { front: "09437", back: "Hita District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0973", back: "Hita District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0973", back: "Hita, Ōita" },
  { front: "0975", back: "Kitaamabe District, Ōita" },
  { front: "09786", back: "Kitsuki, Ōita" },
  { front: "09737", back: "Kusu District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0972", back: "Minamiamabe District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0982", back: "Minamiamabe District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0979", back: "Nakatsu, Ōita" },
  { front: "0974", back: "Naoiri District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0978", back: "Nishikunisaki District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0974", back: "Ono District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0975", back: "Ono District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0975", back: "Ōita District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0977", back: "Ōita District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0975", back: "Ōita, Ōita" },
  { front: "0972", back: "Saiki, Ōita" },
  { front: "0979", back: "Shimoge District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0974", back: "Taketa, Ōita" },
  { front: "0972", back: "Tsukumi, Ōita" },
  { front: "0978", back: "Usa District, Ōita" },
  { front: "0978", back: "Usa, Ōita" },
  { front: "0972", back: "Usuki, Ōita" },
];

const okayama: Card[] = [
  { front: "08687", back: "Aida District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Akaiwa District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08695", back: "Akaiwa District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08699", back: "Akaiwa District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Asakuchi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0865", back: "Asakuchi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08654", back: "Asakuchi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086542", back: "Asakuchi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086554", back: "Asakuchi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Atetsu District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0869", back: "Bizen, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Ibara, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Jobo District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0865", back: "Kasaoka, Okayama" },
  { front: "0868", back: "Katsuta District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08687", back: "Katsuta District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Kawakami District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Kibi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Kibi District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Kojima District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08636", back: "Kojima District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Kume District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0868", back: "Kume District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08687", back: "Kume District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08695", back: "Kume District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Kurashiki, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Maniwa District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Mitsu District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Mitsu District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Niimi, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Oda District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Okayama, Okayama" },
  { front: "08636", back: "Okayama, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Oku District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0869", back: "Oku District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08692", back: "Oku District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086926", back: "Oku District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Shitsuki District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Sōja, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Takahashi, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Tamano, Okayama" },
  { front: "0863", back: "Tamano, Okayama" },
  { front: "0867", back: "Tomata District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0868", back: "Tomata District, Okayama" },
  { front: "086", back: "Tsukubo District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0866", back: "Tsukubo District, Okayama" },
  { front: "0868", back: "Tsuyama, Okayama" },
  { front: "0869", back: "Wake District, Okayama" },
  { front: "08695", back: "Wake District, Okayama" },
];

const okinawa: Card[] = [
  { front: "098", back: "Ginowan, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Gushikawa, Okinawa" },
  { front: "09807", back: "Hirara, Okinawa" },
  { front: "09808", back: "Ishigaki, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Ishikawa, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Itoman, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Kunigami District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "0980", back: "Kunigami District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "09807", back: "Miyako District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "0980", back: "Nago, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Naha, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Nakagami District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Okinawa, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Shimajiri District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "0980", back: "Shimajiri District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "09802", back: "Shimajiri District, Okinawa" },
  { front: "098", back: "Urasoe, Okinawa" },
  { front: "09808", back: "Yaeyama District, Okinawa" },
];

const osaka: Card[] = [
  { front: "072", back: "Daitō, Osaka" },
  { front: "0729", back: "Fujiidera, Osaka" },
  { front: "0729", back: "Habikino, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Hannan, Osaka" },
  { front: "0729", back: "Higashiōsaka District, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Higashiōsaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Higashiōsaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Hirakata, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Ibaraki, Osaka" },
  { front: "0726", back: "Ibaraki, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Ikeda, Osaka" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Ikeda, Osaka" },
  { front: "0725", back: "Izumi, Osaka" },
  { front: "0725", back: "Izumiōtsu, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Izumisano, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Kadoma, Osaka" },
  { front: "0729", back: "Kashiwara, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Katano, Osaka" },
  { front: "0721", back: "Kawachinagano, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Kishiwada, Osaka" },
  { front: "0723", back: "Matsubara, Osaka" },
  { front: "0721", back: "Minamikawachi District, Osaka" },
  { front: "0723", back: "Minamikawachi District, Osaka" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Minoh, Osaka" },
  { front: "075", back: "Mishima District, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Moriguchi, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Neyagawa, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Osaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "0723", back: "Osaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "0723", back: "Ōsakasayama, Osaka" },
  { front: "0722", back: "Sakai, Osaka" },
  { front: "0724", back: "Senboku District, Osaka" },
  { front: "0725", back: "Senboku District, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Sennan District, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Sennan, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Settsu, Osaka" },
  { front: "0726", back: "Settsu, Osaka" },
  { front: "072", back: "Shijōnawate, Osaka" },
  { front: "07437", back: "Shijōnawate, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Suita, Osaka" },
  { front: "0722", back: "Takaishi, Osaka" },
  { front: "0726", back: "Takatsuki, Osaka" },
  { front: "0721", back: "Tondabayashi, Osaka" },
  { front: "0723", back: "Tondabayashi, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Toyonaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Toyonaka, Osaka" },
  { front: "0727", back: "Toyono District, Osaka" },
  { front: "06", back: "Yao, Osaka" },
  { front: "0729", back: "Yao, Osaka" },
];

const saga: Card[] = [
  { front: "0954", back: "Fujitsu District, Saga" },
  { front: "09546", back: "Fujitsu District, Saga" },
  { front: "0955", back: "Higashimatsuura District, Saga" },
  { front: "0955", back: "Imari, Saga" },
  { front: "092", back: "Kanzaki District, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Kanzaki District, Saga" },
  { front: "0955", back: "Karatsu, Saga" },
  { front: "09546", back: "Kashima, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Kishima District, Saga" },
  { front: "0954", back: "Kishima District, Saga" },
  { front: "09546", back: "Kishima District, Saga" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Miyaki District, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Miyaki District, Saga" },
  { front: "0955", back: "Nishimatsuura District, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Ogi District, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Saga District, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Saga, Saga" },
  { front: "0954", back: "Takeo, Saga" },
  { front: "0952", back: "Taku, Saga" },
  { front: "0942", back: "Tosu, Saga" },
];

const saitama: Card[] = [
  { front: "048", back: "Ageo, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Asaka, Saitama" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Chichibu District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0493", back: "Chichibu District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0494", back: "Chichibu District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0494", back: "Chichibu, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Fujimi, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Fujimi, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Fukaya, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Gyōda, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Hannō, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Hanyū, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Hasuda, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Hatogaya, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Hidaka, Saitama" },
  { front: "0493", back: "Higashimatsuyama, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Hiki District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0493", back: "Hiki District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0495", back: "Honjō, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Iruma District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Iruma District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Iruma, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Iwatsuki, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Kamifukuoka, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Kasukabe, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Kawagoe, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Kawagoe, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Kawaguchi, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Kazo, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Kitaadachi District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Kitaadachi District, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Kitakatsushika District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Kitakatsushika District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Kitakatsushika District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Kitamoto, Saitama" },
  { front: "0280", back: "Kitasaitama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Kitasaitama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Kitasaitama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0274", back: "Kodama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0495", back: "Kodama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Konosu, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Koshigaya, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Kuki, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Kumagaya, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Minamisaitama District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Misato, Saitama" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Niiza, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Niiza, Saitama" },
  { front: "0276", back: "Ōsato District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0485", back: "Ōsato District, Saitama" },
  { front: "0493", back: "Ōsato, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Okegawa, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Sakado, Saitama" },
  { front: "0480", back: "Satte, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Sayama, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Shiki, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Sōka, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Toda, Saitama" },
  { front: "0429", back: "Tokorozawa, Saitama" },
  { front: "0492", back: "Tsurugashima, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Urawa, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Wakō, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Warabi, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Yashio, Saitama" },
  { front: "048", back: "Yono, Saitama" },
  { front: "0489", back: "Yoshikawa, Saitama" },
];

const shiga: Card[] = [
  { front: "0748", back: "Echi District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Echi District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0748", back: "Gamo District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Higashiazai District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Hikone, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Ika District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Inukami District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0748", back: "Kanzaki District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0748", back: "Koka District, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Kurita District, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Kusatsu, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Moriyama, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Nagahama, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Ōtsu, Shiga" },
  { front: "0748", back: "Ōmihachiman, Shiga" },
  { front: "0749", back: "Sakata District, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Shiga District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0740", back: "Takashima District, Shiga" },
  { front: "077", back: "Yasu District, Shiga" },
  { front: "0748", back: "Yokaichi, Shiga" },
];

const shimane: Card[] = [
  { front: "0855", back: "Gōtsu, Shimane" },
  { front: "0855", back: "Hamada, Shimane" },
  { front: "0853", back: "Hikawa District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0853", back: "Hirata, Shimane" },
  { front: "0854", back: "Iishi District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0853", back: "Izumo, Shimane" },
  { front: "08567", back: "Kanoashi District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0856", back: "Masuda, Shimane" },
  { front: "0852", back: "Matsue, Shimane" },
  { front: "0856", back: "Mino District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0855", back: "Naka District, Shimane" },
  { front: "08548", back: "Nima District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0855", back: "Nima District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0854", back: "Nita District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0854", back: "Nogi District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0855", back: "Ōchi District, Shimane" },
  { front: "08548", back: "Ōda, Shimane" },
  { front: "0854", back: "Ohara District, Shimane" },
  { front: "08514", back: "Oki District, Shimane" },
  { front: "0854", back: "Yasugi, Shimane" },
  { front: "0852", back: "Yatsuka District, Shimane" },
];

const shizuoka: Card[] = [
  { front: "0465", back: "Atami, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0557", back: "Atami, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "054", back: "Fuji District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0545", back: "Fuji, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "054", back: "Fujieda, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0544", back: "Fujinomiya, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0538", back: "Fukuroi, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0550", back: "Gotemba, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0547", back: "Haibara District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0548", back: "Haibara District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "053", back: "Hamamatsu, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "053", back: "Hamana District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0543", back: "Ihara District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0545", back: "Ihara District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0538", back: "Iwata District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0539", back: "Iwata District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0538", back: "Iwata, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0537", back: "Kakegawa, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0557", back: "Kamo District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0558", back: "Kamo District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "053", back: "Kosai, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0559", back: "Mishima, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0559", back: "Numazu, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0537", back: "Ogasa District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0538", back: "Ogasa District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0547", back: "Ogasa District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0548", back: "Ogasa District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "054", back: "Shida District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0547", back: "Shimada, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0543", back: "Shimizu, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0558", back: "Shimoda, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "054", back: "Shizuoka, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0538", back: "Shuchi District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0539", back: "Shuchi District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0550", back: "Sunto District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0559", back: "Sunto District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0559", back: "Susono, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0557", back: "Tagata District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0558", back: "Tagata District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0559", back: "Tagata District, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "0539", back: "Tenryū, Shizuoka" },
  { front: "054", back: "Yaizu, Shizuoka" },
];

const tochigi: Card[] = [
  { front: "0284", back: "Ashikaga, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0283", back: "Aso District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "028", back: "Haga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0285", back: "Haga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0288", back: "Imaichi, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0282", back: "Kamitsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0288", back: "Kamitsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0289", back: "Kamitsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0289", back: "Kanuma, Tochigi" },
  { front: "028", back: "Kawachi District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0285", back: "Kawachi District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Kuroiso, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0285", back: "Mooka, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Nasu District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0288", back: "Nikkō, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Ōtawara, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0280", back: "Oyama, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0282", back: "Oyama, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0285", back: "Oyama, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0296", back: "Oyama, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0283", back: "Sano, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0280", back: "Shimotsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0282", back: "Shimotsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0285", back: "Shimotsuga District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "028", back: "Shioya District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Shioya District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0288", back: "Shioya District, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0282", back: "Tochigi, Tochigi" },
  { front: "028", back: "Utsunomiya, Tochigi" },
  { front: "0287", back: "Yaita, Tochigi" },
];

const tokushima: Card[] = [
  { front: "0884", back: "Anan, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0883", back: "Awa District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Itano District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08847", back: "Kaifu District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08854", back: "Katsura District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08853", back: "Komatsushima, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Komatsushima, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0883", back: "Mima District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0883", back: "Miyoshi District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Miyoshi District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Myodo District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Myozai District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0884", back: "Naka District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08846", back: "Naka District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08853", back: "Naka District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Naruto, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0883", back: "Oe District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "08853", back: "Tokushima District, Tokushima" },
  { front: "0886", back: "Tokushima, Tokushima" },
];

const tokyo: Card[] = [
  { front: "042", back: "Akiruno, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Akishima, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0422", back: "Chōfu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Chōfu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Fuchu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Fuchu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Fuchu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Fussa, Tokyo" },
  { front: "04996", back: "Hachiōji, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Hachiōji, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0426", back: "Hachiōji, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Hamura, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Higashikurume, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Higashimurayama, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Higashiyamato, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Hino, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0422", back: "Hoya, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Hoya, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Inagi, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Kiyose, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Kodaira, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Kodaira, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0422", back: "Koganei, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Koganei, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Kokubunji, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Kokubunji, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Kokuritsu, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Konoe, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Machida, Tokyo" },
  { front: "044", back: "Machida, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0422", back: "Mitaka, Tokyo" },
  { front: "04994", back: "Miyake, Tokyocho" },
  { front: "042", back: "Musashimurayama, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0422", back: "Musashino, Tokyo" },
  { front: "042", back: "Nishitama, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0428", back: "Nishitama, Tokyo" },
  { front: "04998", back: "Ogasawara, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0428", back: "Ōme, Tokyo" },
  { front: "04992", back: "Ōshima, Tokyocho" },
  { front: "042", back: "Tachikawa, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0423", back: "Tama, Tokyo" },
  { front: "0424", back: "Tanashi, Tokyo" },
  { front: "03", back: "Tokyo" },
];

const tottori: Card[] = [
  { front: "0859", back: "Hino District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0857", back: "Iwami District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0857", back: "Ketaka District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0858", back: "Kurayoshi, Tottori" },
  { front: "0858", back: "Saihaku District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0859", back: "Saihaku District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0859", back: "Sakaiminato, Tottori" },
  { front: "0858", back: "Tōhaku District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0857", back: "Tottori, Tottori" },
  { front: "0858", back: "Yazu District, Tottori" },
  { front: "0859", back: "Yonago, Tottori" },
];

const toyama: Card[] = [
  { front: "0763", back: "Higashitonami District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Himi, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Imizu District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0764", back: "Kaminiikawa District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0765", back: "Kurobe, Toyama" },
  { front: "0764", back: "Nakaniikawa District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0764", back: "Namerikawa, Toyama" },
  { front: "0764", back: "Nei District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0763", back: "Nishitonami District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Oyabe, Toyama" },
  { front: "0765", back: "Shimoniikawa District, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Shinminato, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Takaoka, Toyama" },
  { front: "0763", back: "Tonami, Toyama" },
  { front: "0764", back: "Toyama, Toyama" },
  { front: "0766", back: "Toyama, Toyama" },
  { front: "0765", back: "Uozu, Toyama" },
];

const wakayama: Card[] = [
  { front: "0737", back: "Arida District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0737", back: "Arida, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0738", back: "Gobō, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0736", back: "Hashimoto, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0738", back: "Hidaka District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0739", back: "Hidaka District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "05979", back: "Higashimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "07354", back: "Higashimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "073549", back: "Higashimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "07355", back: "Higashimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "07357", back: "Higashimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0736", back: "Ito District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0737", back: "Ito District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0734", back: "Kainan, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0734", back: "Kaiso District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0736", back: "Naga District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "07356", back: "Nishimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0739", back: "Nishimuro District, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0735", back: "Shingū, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0739", back: "Tanabe, Wakayama" },
  { front: "0734", back: "Wakayama, Wakayama" },
];

const yamagata: Card[] = [
  { front: "0234", back: "Akumi District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "023", back: "Higashimurayama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0236", back: "Higashimurayama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Higashimurayama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Higashine, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0238", back: "Higashiokitama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0234", back: "Higashitagawa District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0235", back: "Higashitagawa District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "023", back: "Kaminoyama, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Kitamurayama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "023", back: "Mogami District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0234", back: "Mogami District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Murayama, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0238", back: "Nagai, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0238", back: "Nan'yō, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Nishimurayama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0238", back: "Nishiokitama District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0235", back: "Nishitagawa District, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Obanazawa, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Sagae, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0234", back: "Sakata, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0233", back: "Shinjō, Yamagata" },
  { front: "023", back: "Tendō, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0237", back: "Tendō, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0235", back: "Tsuruoka, Yamagata" },
  { front: "023", back: "Yamagata, Yamagata" },
  { front: "0238", back: "Yonezawa, Yamagata" },
];

const yamaguchi: Card[] = [
  { front: "0838", back: "Abu District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08387", back: "Abu District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08388", back: "Abu District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08395", back: "Abu District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0836", back: "Asa District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0838", back: "Hagi, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0833", back: "Hikari, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0835", back: "Hōfu, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0827", back: "Iwakuni, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08275", back: "Iwakuni, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0820", back: "Kuga District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0827", back: "Kuga District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08275", back: "Kuga District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0820", back: "Kumage District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0833", back: "Kumage District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08376", back: "Mine District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08396", back: "Mine District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08375", back: "Mine, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0837", back: "Nagato, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08207", back: "Ōshima District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0837", back: "Otsu District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0836", back: "Onoda, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0835", back: "Saba District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0832", back: "Shimonoseki, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0833", back: "Shimonoseki, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0834", back: "Shinnan'yō, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0834", back: "Tokuyama, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0832", back: "Toyora District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0837", back: "Toyora District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "08376", back: "Toyora District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0834", back: "Tsuno District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0836", back: "Ube, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0839", back: "Yamaguchi, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0820", back: "Yanai, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0836", back: "Yoshiki District, Yamaguchi" },
  { front: "0839", back: "Yoshiki District, Yamaguchi" },
];

const yamanashi: Card[] = [
  { front: "0553", back: "Enzan, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0555", back: "Fujiyoshida, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0553", back: "Higashiyamanashi District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0552", back: "Higashiyatsushiro District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0266", back: "Kitakoma District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0551", back: "Kitakoma District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0428", back: "Kitatsuru District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0552", back: "Kōfu, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0556", back: "Minamikoma District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0427", back: "Minamitsuru District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0554", back: "Minamitsuru District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0555", back: "Minamitsuru District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0552", back: "Nakakoma District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0551", back: "Nirasaki, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0555", back: "Nishiyatsushiro District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0552", back: "Nishiyatsushiro District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0556", back: "Nishiyatsushiro District, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0554", back: "Ōtsuki, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0554", back: "Tsuru, Yamanashi" },
  { front: "0553", back: "Yamanashi, Yamanashi" },
];

const cards: Card[] = [
  ...aichi,
  ...akita,
  ...aomori,
  ...chiba,
  ...ehime,
  ...fukui,
  ...fukuoka,
  ...fukushima,
  ...gifu,
  ...gunma,
  ...hiroshima,
  ...hokkaido,
  ...hyogo,
  ...ibaraki,
  ...ishikawa,
  ...iwate,
  ...kagawa,
  ...kagoshima,
  ...kanagawa,
  ...kochi,
  ...kumamoto,
  ...kyoto,
  ...mie,
  ...miyagi,
  ...miyazaki,
  ...nagano,
  ...nagasaki,
  ...nara,
  ...niigata,
  ...oita,
  ...okayama,
  ...okinawa,
  ...osaka,
  ...saga,
  ...saitama,
  ...shiga,
  ...shimane,
  ...shizuoka,
  ...tochigi,
  ...tokushima,
  ...tokyo,
  ...tottori,
  ...toyama,
  ...wakayama,
  ...yamagata,
  ...yamaguchi,
  ...yamanashi,
];

function AreaCodesJP() {
  return (
    <Tip>
      <Head>
        <h1>Area Codes</h1>
        <Separator />
        <TrainingModal cards={cards} />
        <MapButton url="https://www.geoguessr.com/maps/63f0df59691f7c8623484ab8" />
      </Head>
      <Paragraph>
        <em>
          The training set is very complete with {cards.length} area codes. It is enough to just recall the prefecture
          as a first exercice, which is always written at the end!
        </em>
        <br />
        <br />
        The leading 0 is omitted when calling from outside Japan. Cell phones use the dialing codes of 070, 080 or 090.
        IP-based phone services use the 050 dialing code. Area codes ending with a 0 are often not regional, most
        notably 0120.
        <br />
        <br />
        <h3>Length of numbers</h3>
        <ul>
          <li>Special numbers are three digits long</li>
          <li>
            <strong>Geographic numbers are ten digits long, including the area code and the leading zero. </strong>
            Consequently, densely populated areas have shorter area codes, while less populated areas have longer area
            codes. For example:
            <ul>
              <li style={{ marginLeft: "1rem" }}>06 xxxx xxxx (Osaka)</li>
              <li style={{ marginLeft: "1rem" }}>075 xxx xxxx (Kyoto)</li>
              <li style={{ marginLeft: "1rem" }}>0742 xx xxxx (Nara)</li>
              <li style={{ marginLeft: "1rem" }}>04992 x xxxx (Niijima island, Tokyo pref.)</li>
              <li style={{ marginLeft: "1rem" }}>082486 xxxx (Takano, Hiroshima pref.)</li>
            </ul>
          </li>
          <li>0x0 Non-geographic numbers are 10 -or- 11 digits long.</li>
          <li>0xx0 Non-geographic numbers are 10 digits long</li>
        </ul>
      </Paragraph>
      <ImageMagnifier src={Map} alt="Map of Japan with area codes" style={{ backgroundColor: "var(--purple-200)" }} />
    </Tip>
  );
}

export default AreaCodesJP;
